<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">ID-a-Key</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="e_mail">Email:</string>
    <string name="password">Password:</string>
    <string name="repeat_password">Repeat Password:</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="already_have_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="iqe_app_key">4cb870a67b43493aa668e94ca9095b18</string>
    <string name="iqe_app_secret">c001b534b5f34f788653cf26c2ea9172</string>
    <string name="desclaimer">"Five Tykes Technologies, LLC
Software License Agreement for ID-a-Key Application

Please read this software license agreement (\"License\") carefully before using the ID-a-Key application software. By using the ID-a-Key application software, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of this License. If you do not agree to the terms of this License, do not use the software. If you do not agree to the terms of the License, you may express this by clicking \"disagree/decline\" at your initial sign-in to the program. In the event you have purchased this application but declined acceptance of these terms, your right to use the application will immediately terminate and the application will not be activated.  However, you will be entitled to a refund of the purchase price of the application.  In order to obtain a refund, you must make your refund request in writing and send it to Five Tykes Technologies, LLC (“FTT”), at PO Box 25578, Dallas, TX 75225.  Please provide your name and mailing address so that refunds can be forwarded to you; you must allow six weeks for delivery from the date of receipt of the refund request.

1. General. The ID-a-Key application and any third party software, documentation and any fonts accompanying this License, whether on disk, in read only memory, on any other media or in any other form, including any upgrades or updates sold or provided by FTT (collectively the \"ID-a-Key application software\"), are licensed, not sold, to you by FTT for use only under the terms of this License. FTT reserves all rights not expressly granted to you. The terms of this License will govern any software upgrades provided by FTT that replace and/or supplement the original ID-a-Key application software product, unless such upgrade is accompanied by a separate license in which case the terms of that license will govern.  

Title and intellectual property rights in and to any content displayed by or accessed through the ID-a-Key application software, and all associated trademarks and trade dress, belong to the respective content owner.  Such content may be protected by copyright or other intellectual property laws and treaties, and may be subject to terms of use of the third party providing such content. This License does not grant you any rights to use such content.

2. Permitted License Uses and Restrictions. 
A. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, you are granted a limited, per-user, non-exclusive license to install and use the ID-a-Key application software. You may not make the ID-a-Key application software available over a network where it could be available to or used by multiple devices or unlicensed users.  This license is only authorized with regard to the phone or device from which the license was originally purchased, or any replacement thereof.

B. You may not, and you agree not to, or to enable others to, copy (except as expressly permitted by this License), decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, attempt to derive the source code of, decrypt, modify, create derivative works of the ID-a-Key application software, or any part thereof (except as and only to the extent any foregoing restriction is prohibited by applicable law or to the extent as may be permitted by licensing terms governing use of open-sourced components included with the ID-a-Key application software).  Any attempt to do so is a violation of the rights of FTT and its licensors of the ID-a-Key application software.

C. The ID-a-Key application Software may not be modified without the prior written permission of FTT.  FTT is not obligated to provide any maintenance, technical or other support for modified ID-a-Key application software.

D. The ID-a-Key application software may not be used to copy or reproduce keys to property that does not belong to the licensee without the express permission of the owner of the keys or the property itself, and any use of the application for trespass, theft, unlawful entry or other criminal act against persons is expressly prohibited and constitutes grounds for immediate termination of the license by FTT without further notice. FTT shall not be held responsible for any unlawful use of the ID-a-key software. If you are uncertain about your right to copy or permit access to any material, you should contact your legal advisor. 


3. Transfer. You may not rent, lease, lend, redistribute or sublicense the ID-a-Key application software. 

4. Consent to Use of Data. 
A. Diagnostic and Usage Data. By agreeing to the terms and conditions of this document, you agree that FTT and its agents may collect, maintain, process and use diagnostic, technical, usage and related information, including but not limited to information about your smartphone device, and system and application software, that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support and other services to you (if any) related to the ID-a-Key application software, and to verify compliance with the terms of this License. FTT may use this information, as long as it is collected in a form that does not personally identify you, to provide and improve FTT's products and services.

B. Privacy Policy. At all times your application data will be treated as confidential.

5. Services. 
A. This application may not be available in all languages or in all countries. Furthermore, use of the ID-a-key application software requires a telephone with a suitable camera capability, a compatible operating system, Internet access and sufficient bandwidth (“Operating Requirements”).  FTT is not responsible for any failure of the application as a consequence of any failure to licensee’s device to meet the Operating Requirements.  Expansion of program capability may require an Apple or Google Play ID, may require you to accept additional terms of service, and may be subject to additional fees; FTT shall not be responsible for obtaining any such items for the licensee.

B. FTT may display, include or make available content, data, information, applications or materials from third parties (“Third Party Materials”) or provide links to certain third party web sites. You acknowledge and agree that FTT is not responsible for examining or evaluating the content, accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any other aspect of such Third Party Materials or web sites. FTT and its officers, members, managers, affiliates and subsidiaries do not warrant or endorse, and do not assume and will not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person for, any third-party services, Third Party Materials or web sites, or for any other materials, products, or services of third parties. Third Party Materials and links to other web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. You agree that you will not use any Third Party Materials in a manner that would infringe or violate the rights of any other party, and that FTT is not in any way responsible for any such use by you.

C. You agree that the ID-a-Key application Software, including but not limited to graphics, photographs, trademarks and trade dress, and editorial content, constitute or contain proprietary content, information and material that is owned by FTT and/or its licensors, and is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws, including but not limited to copyright. You agree that you will not infringe upon any intellectual property rights of a third party or FTT. You shall not exploit the ID-a-Key application in any unauthorized way whatsoever, including but not limited to, using the application to transmit any computer viruses, worms, trojan horses or other malware, or by trespass or burdening network capacity. You further agree not to use the software in any manner to harass, abuse, stalk, threaten, defame or otherwise infringe or violate the rights of any other party, and that FTT is not in any way responsible for any such use by you, nor for any harassing, threatening, defamatory, offensive, infringing or illegal messages or transmissions that you may receive as a result of using any aspect of the software.  
		
D. In addition, software functionality and Third Party Materials that may be accessed from, displayed on or linked to from the ID-a-Key application Software are not available in all languages or in all countries or regions. FTT makes no representation that such software and Materials are appropriate or available for use in any particular location, especially since Internet access of sufficient bandwidth is required for full application function. FTT and its licensors reserve the right to change, suspend, remove, or disable access to any ID-a-Key services at any time without notice. In no event will FTT be liable for the removal or disabling of access to any such services. FTT may also impose limits on the use of or access to certain services, in any case and without notice or liability. 

6. Termination. This License is effective until terminated. Your rights under this License will terminate automatically without notice from FTT if you fail to comply with any term(s) of this License. Upon the termination of this License, you must cease all use of the ID-a-Key application software. Sections 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 11 and 12 of this License shall survive any such termination.

7. Disclaimer of Warranties. 
A. If you are a customer who is a consumer (someone who uses the ID-a-Key application software outside of your trade, business or profession), you may have legal rights in your country of residence which would prohibit the following limitations from applying to you, and where prohibited they will not apply to you. To find out more about rights, you should contact a local consumer advice organization.

B. YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, PURCHASE AND USE OF THE ID-A-KEY SOFTWARE APPLICATION IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK, AND THAT THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY AND EFFORT IS WITH YOU.
The ID-a-Key application Software may not correctly identify objects with 100% accuracy. FTT will not be held responsible for application inaccuracy or malfunction, nor will FTT be held responsible for any consequences stemming from product inaccuracy or malfunction, nor will FTT be required or responsible to provide licensee with any form of compensation or reimbursement for product malfunction and/or loss of information, nor will FTT be responsible for any damages or consequential losses arising therefrom.
 
C. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE ID-A-KEY SOFTWARE AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED \"AS IS\" AND “AS AVAILABLE”, WITH ALL FAULTS AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, AND FTT AND ITS LICENSORS (COLLECTIVELY REFERRED TO AS \"FTT\" FOR THE PURPOSES OF SECTIONS 7 AND 8) HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE ID-A-KEY SOFTWARE AND SERVICES, EITHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND/OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, ACCURACY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. 

D. FTT DOES NOT WARRANT AGAINST INTERFERENCE WITH YOUR USE OF THE FTT SOFTWARE AND SERVICES, THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN OR SERVICES PERFORMED BY THE FTT SOFTWARE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, THAT THE OPERATION OF THE FTT SOFTWARE AND SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT ANY SERVICE WILL CONTINUE TO BE MADE AVAILABLE, THAT DEFECTS IN THE FTT SOFTWARE OR SERVICES WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE FTT ID-A-KEY SOFTWARE WILL BE COMPATIBLE OR WORK WITH ANY THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS OR THIRD PARTY SERVICES. INSTALLATION OF THIS SOFTWARE MAY AFFECT THE USABILITY OF THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS OR THIRD PARTY SERVICES.  

E. YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE FTT SOFTWARE AND SERVICES ARE NOT INTENDED OR SUITABLE FOR USE IN SITUATIONS OR ENVIRONMENTS WHERE THE FAILURE OR TIME DELAYS OF, OR ERRORS OR INACCURACIES IN, THE CONTENT, DATA OR INFORMATION PROVIDED BY THE FTT SOFTWARE OR SERVICES COULD LEAD TO DEATH, PERSONAL INJURY, OR SEVERE PHYSICAL OR ENVIRONMENTAL DAMAGE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE OPERATION OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES, AIRCRAFT NAVIGATION OR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS, AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL, LIFE SUPPORT OR WEAPONS SYSTEMS.

F. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY FTT OR AN FTT AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY TO LICENSEE, AND LICENSEE DISCLAIMS AND WAIVES ANY RIGHT TO RELY ON ANY REPRESENTATIONS, PROMISES, COVENANTS OR STATEMENTS NOT SET FORTH HEREIN.  SHOULD THE FTT APPLICATION SOFTWARE OR SERVICES PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS ON APPLICABLE STATUTORY RIGHTS OF A CONSUMER, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.  


8. Limitation of Liability. TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL FTT BE LIABLE FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, CORRUPTION OR LOSS OF DATA, FAILURE TO TRANSMIT OR RECEIVE ANY DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION OR ANY OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL PERSONAL OR COMMERCIAL DAMAGES OR LOSSES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE ID-A-KEY SOFTWARE OR SERVICES OR ANY THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE OR APPLICATIONS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE FTT SOFTWARE, HOWEVER CAUSED, REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY (CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE) AND EVEN IF FTT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THIS LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. In no event shall FTT’s total liability to you for all damages (other than as may be required by applicable law in cases involving personal injury) exceed the amount of fifty dollars ($50.00). The foregoing limitations will apply even if the above stated remedy fails of its essential purpose.

9. Export Control. You may not use or otherwise export or reexport the ID-a-Key Software except as authorized by United States law and the laws of the jurisdiction in which the FTT Software was obtained. In particular, but without limitation, the FTT Software may not be exported or re-exported (a) into any U.S. embargoed countries or (b) to anyone on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals or the U.S. Department of Commerce Denied Person’s List or Entity List. By using the FTT Software, you represent and warrant that you are not located in any such country or on any such list. You also agree that you will not use the FTT Software for any purposes prohibited by United States law, including, without limitation, the development, design, manufacture or production of missiles, or nuclear, chemical or biological weapons.

10. Government End Users. The FTT Software and related documentation are \"Commercial Items\", as that term is defined at 48 C.F.R. §2.101, consisting of \"Commercial Computer Software\" and \"Commercial Computer Software Documentation\", as such terms are used in 48 C.F.R. §12.212 or 48 C.F.R. §227.7202, as applicable.  Consistent with 48 C.F.R. §12.212 or 48 C.F.R. §227.7202-1 through 227.7202-4, as applicable, the Commercial Computer Software and Commercial Computer Software Documentation are being licensed to U.S. Government end users (a) only as Commercial Items and (b) with only those rights as are granted to all other end users pursuant to the terms and conditions herein. Unpublished-rights reserved under the copyright laws of the United States.

11. Controlling Law and Severability. This License will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Texas. This License shall not be governed by the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, the application of which is expressly excluded.  If you are a consumer based in the United Kingdom, this License will be governed by the laws of the jurisdiction of your residence. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision, or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, the remainder of this License shall continue in full force and effect.  

12. Complete Agreement; Governing Language. This License constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the use of the ID-a-Key software licensed hereunder and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous understandings regarding such subject matter, with the exception of any additional terms and conditions you are required to accept if you choose to use Apple's or Google Play’s online store which will govern your use of such store and any Services you purchase through that store. No amendment to or modification of this License will be binding unless in writing and signed by FTT. Any translation of this License is done for local requirements and in the event of a dispute between the English and any non-English versions, the English version of this License shall govern, to the extent not prohibited by local law in your jurisdiction.

13. Third Party Software and Service Terms and Conditions.
Portions of the FTT Software utilize or include third party software and other copyrighted material. Your use of such material is governed by their respective terms. YOU AGREE NOT TO USE OR EXPLOIT THIRD PARTY VENDOR DATA, SOFTWARE, OR SERVERS, EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PERMITTED HEREIN. If you violate these restrictions, your non-exclusive license to use third party software and accompanying data will terminate.

All third party software is utilized through the ID-a-Key application \"AS IS.\" FTT and third party vendors make no representations or warranties, express or implied, regarding the accuracy of any data in their servers. In addition, FTT and third party vendors reserve the right to delete data from servers or to change data categories for any cause deemed sufficient.  No warranty is made that the FTT or third party software or servers are error-free or that functioning of such software or servers will be uninterrupted. FTT and third party vendors are not obligated to provide you with new, enhanced, or additional data types or categories that each company may provide in the future, and each company is free to discontinue its services at any time. FTT AND THIRD PARTY VENDORS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. FTT AND THIRD PARTY VENDORS DO NOT WARRANT THE RESULTS THAT WILL BE OBTAINED BY YOUR USE OF THE ID-A-KEY SOFTWARE OR ANY ASSOCIATED SERVER. IN NO CASE WILL FTT BE LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES OR FOR ANY LOST PROFITS OR LOST REVENUES. 

If your license terminates, you agree to cease any and all use of third party vendor data, software, and servers. Furthermore, third party vendors reserve all rights relative to any and all data in their system, software, and servers, including all ownership rights.  Under no circumstances will third party vendors become liable for any payment to you for any information that you provide or have provided through ID-a-Key software use. All third party vendors may enforce their rights under this agreement against you directly in their own name. "</string>
    <string name="tutorial_text">   
<b>Not sure what all the keys on your keychain go to anymore? Too many keys to keep up with? </b><br/>

ID-a-Key solves these problems by storing and identifying keys entered into your smartphone.  Entries are made using your phone’s built-in camera. Then, at any time or place thereafter, you can take a picture of an unknown key and the app will identify it for you.

There are several main functions of the ID-a-Key app:

1. Creating an ID-a-Key account,
2. Adding additional key capability via in-app purchase,
2. Entering new keys into your phone,
3. Identifying a previously labeled key,
4. Viewing or searching within your key list,
5. Viewing your category list,

<b>Creating an ID-a-Key Account</b>
The first time you open the ID-a-Key app, you will be prompted to:
a. accept the Five Tykes Technologies license agreement, 
b. enter your email address (for purposes of identification of your key set), and 
c. create a password for entry into the program. 

Once these steps are completed, you will be taken to the Home screen for further navigation. 

Please save your login information. If you forget your password, you will have to create a new one which will be sent to you at your email address. 

<b>Adding Keys via In-App Purchases</b>
Your purchase of the ID-a-Key app entitles you to enter 2 keys for storage and later identification. If you wish to purchase additional storage capability, select the “My Account” tab. You will see several options for adding keys. Once you make your selection, your payment will be processed through your iTunes or Google Play account.

<b>Entering New Keys</b>
Place your key flat on a white background with good lighting.  Touch the “Add New Key” button either from the Home screen or from the Tab Menu.  Center the image within the key silhouette for best results, and take the picture (the flash is automatically suppressed to prevent distortion).   Then choose either “Use” or “Retake.”  Once the picture is selected, a Key Name and Category (optional) can be added.  Selecting “Save” sends the key image and details to your database for storage. 

<b>Identifying a Key</b>
Place the key flat on a white background with good lighting.  Touch the “Identify a Key” button either from the Home page or the Tab Menu.  Once the key is centered in the key silhouette, take the picture.   Then select either “Use” or “Retake.”  When the “Use” button is selected, the app will search your database.  If the key has been previously entered, the app will identify it and display the associated label information.  If the key is not found, the app will allow the user to enter it into the system.

<b>Viewing Your List of Keys</b>
Select the “Key Listing” button from the Home screen or the Keys tab button to see a list of all stored keys.  The default system lists keys by date of entry, though they can be organized and sorted by number, name, date and category.  There is also a search button that allows search by key name.

<b>Viewing Your List of Categories</b>
Keys entered into the app can be organized according to category.  Each key detail screen identifies the key’s category (optional), and the key list page displays category assignments.  In order to view the categories, touch the “Categories” button on the Home screen or the Key List page.  This will bring up all the Categories with a notation of how many keys are in each category.  Selecting a category enables  viewing of all the keys in that category.  Categories can be edited by selecting the “Edit” button on the Categories screen.  Touching the green “Plus” button adds a new category.  Selecting the category name brings up the “Edit Category Name” screen.  The red “Delete” button appears next to each category—selecting this button will delete the category.  (Please note that categories with keys in them cannot be deleted.  Similarly, the default “Unassigned” category cannot be edited/deleted.)
</string>
<string  name="web_text">    
<h2>
Not sure what all the keys on your keychain go to anymore? Too many keys to keep up with? 
</h2>
<p>ID-a-Key solves these problems by storing and identifying keys entered into your smartphone.  Entries are made using your phone’s built-in camera. Then, at any time or place thereafter, you can take a picture of an unknown key and the app will identify it for you.</p><br/>

<p>There are several main functions of the ID-a-Key app:</p><br/>
<ol>
<li>Creating an ID-a-Key account,</li>
<li>Adding additional key capability via in-app purchase,</li>
<li> Entering new keys into your phone,</li>
<li>Identifying a previously labeled key,</li>
<li>Viewing or searching within your key list,</li>
<li>Viewing your category list,</li>
</ol>
</string>

</resources>